A Guide to the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) records FA084
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEC Audio Files, 1987-2003; 12
  - Ray Allen Goldberg, 2002 October 15; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15965)
  - Robert Helander - Part 1, 2002 July 10; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15966)
  - Robert Helander - Part 2, 2002 July 10; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15967)
  - Robert Helander - Part 3, 2002 July 10; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15968)
  - John Hultkrans, 2002 October 18; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15969)
  - Edward Kimball, 2002 October 23; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15970)
  - E. Kennedy Langstaff, 2002-November 18; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15971)
  - Arlen Loselle, 2002 September 20; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15972)
  - Donald E. Meads - Part 1, 2002 August 20; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15973)
  - Donald E. Meads - Part 2, 2002 August 20; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15974)
  - George O'Neill, 2003 April 16; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15975)
  - Andrea Pampanini - Part 1, 2002 October 3; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15976)
  - Andrea Pampanini - Part 2, 2002 October 3; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15977)
  - Rodman Rockefeller, 1987 August 4; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15978)
  - Ruth Ryer, 2002 September 19; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15979)
  - Harvey Schwartz - Part 1, 2002 October 2; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15980)
  - Harvey Schwartz - Part 2, 2002 October 2; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15981)
  - Jonathan Taylor, 2002 December 9; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15982)
  - I. H. von Zelowitz - Part 1, 2002 September 17; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15983)
  - I. H. von Zelowitz - Part 2, 2002 September 17; 1/8 inch audio cassette; Sound (Box 1, Tape AV 15984)
- Oral Histories, 13
  - IBEC Oral History Interviews - Bass - Goldberg (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - IBEC Oral History Interviews - Helander - Meads (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - IBEC Oral History Interviews - Pampanini - von Zelowitz (Box 2, Folder 1)